{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the ninja protagonist in Naruto?",
      "answers": [
        "Sasuke Uchiha",
        "Sakura Haruno",
        "Naruto Uzumaki",
        "Kakashi Hatake"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "In Dragon Ball Z, what is the signature attack of Goku?",
      "answers": [
        "Final Flash",
        "Kamehameha",
        "Spirit Bomb",
        "Big Bank Attack"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the main character in One Piece?",
      "answers": ["Zoro", "Sanji", "Luffy", "Nami"],
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the title of the anime about a young boy named Gon Freecss?",
      "answers": ["Naruto", "Bleach", "Fairy Tail", "Hunter x Hunter"],
      "correctAnswer": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "In Sailor Moon, what is the civilian name of the titular character?",
      "answers": ["Serena Tsukino", "Rei Hino", "Minako Aino", "Ami Mizuno"],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the main setting of Attack on Titan?",
      "answers": ["Paradis Island", "Marley", "Siganshina District", "Walls"],
      "correctAnswer": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Name the magical girl anime where the protagonist's weapon is a talking cat named Luna.",
      "answers": [
        "Cardcaptor Sakura",
        "Puella Magi Madoka Magica",
        "Sailer Moon",
        "Tokyo Mew Mew"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "In My Hero Academia, what is the main character, Izuku Midoriya, commonly known as?",
      "answers": ["All Might", "Kacchan", "Deku", "Endeavor"],
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which anime features a group of pirates led by Monkey D. Luffy?",
      "answers": ["Fairy Tail", "One Piece", "Black Clover", "Bleach"],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the main character's name in Bleach?",
      "answers": ["Ichigo", "Renji", "Rukia", "Chad"],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What anime are is the main characters brother in a suit of armor?",
      "answers": ["One Piece", "Full Metal Alchemist", "Naruto", "Tokyo Ghoul"],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which anime features a group of students trying to assassinate their tentacled teacher, Koro-sensei?",
      "answers": [
        "My Hero Academia",
        "Assassination Classroom",
        "Classroom of the Elite",
        "Blue Exorcist"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "In Death Note, what alias does Light Yagami use when reffering to the notebook's power?",
      "answers": ["Kira", "Shinigami", "L", "Ryuk"],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the mysterious organization in Steins;Gate?",
      "answers": ["SERN", "Future Gadget Lab", "Rounders", "Lab Members 001"],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which anime follows the story of Edward and Alphonse Elric, who use alchemy to find the Philosopher's Stone?",
      "answers": [
        "Attack on Titan",
        "Fullmetal Alchemist",
        "Code Geass",
        "Tokyo Ghoul"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "In Cowboy Bebop, what is Spike Spiegel's former profession?",
      "answers": ["Hitman", "Bounty Hunter", "Police Officer", "Smuggler"],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the central theme of the anime Neon Genesis Evangelion?",
      "answers": [
        "Mecha Battles",
        "Friendship",
        "Existentialism",
        "Time Travel"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "In the anime Your Lie in April, what instrument does the main character Kosei Arima play?",
      "answers": ["Violin", "Guitar", "Piano", "Flute"],
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the virtual reality MMORPG in Sword Art Online?",
      "answers": [
        "Alfheim Online",
        "Gun Gale Online",
        "Aincrad",
        "Accel World"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which anime explores the themes of artificial intelligence and the blurred line between man and machine?",
      "answers": [
        "Ghost in the Shell",
        "Serial Experiments Lain",
        "Ergo Proxy",
        "Psycho-Pass"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "In 'Neon Genesis Evangelion,' what is the ultimate goal of the mysterious organization SEELE?",
      "answers": [
        "Human Instrumentality Project",
        "World Domination",
        "Eradicate Angels",
        "Create Superhumans"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which anime features a complex game called 'The Sekai Seifuku: Bouryaku no Zvezda'?",
      "answers": [
        "World Conquest Zvezda Plot",
        "No Game No Life",
        "Log Horizon",
        "Btooom!"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "In 'Monster,' what is the name of the elusive criminal Dr. Kenzo Tenma is searching for?",
      "answers": [
        "Johan Liebert",
        "Yohan Albert",
        "Heinrich Braun",
        "Martin Schneider"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which anime explores the impact of mental illnesses on the characters, including borderline personality disorder?",
      "answers": [
        "Welcome to the NHK",
        "Paranoia Agent",
        "March Comes in Like a Lion",
        "Perfect Blue"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the main plot device in 'Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magica' that twists the magical girl genre?",
      "answers": [
        "Time Travel",
        "Witch Hunts",
        "Contract with Kyubey",
        "Parallel Universes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "In 'Serial Experiments Lain,' what is the virtual world that blurs the boundary between reality and the Wired?",
      "answers": ["The Wired", "The Matrix", "The Deep Web", "The Other Side"],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which anime explores the consequences of altering timelines and the concept of 'D-mails'?",
      "answers": [
        "Puella Magi Madoka Magica",
        "Steins;Gate",
        "Erased",
        "Re:Zero"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the elite school in 'The Irregular at Magic High School' that segregates students based on magical ability?",
      "answers": [
        "First High School",
        "Magic Academy",
        "Nine Schools Competition",
        "Bloom vs. Weed"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "In 'Cowboy Bebop,' what is the significance of the term 'Julia' in Spike Spiegel's past?",
      "answers": [
        "Code Name",
        "Lost Love",
        "Bounty Target",
        "Secret Organization"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which anime involves the 'Mushi,' ethereal creatures that exist beyond the perception of most humans?",
      "answers": [
        "Natsume's Book of Friends",
        "Mushishi",
        "Mononoke",
        "Kino's Journey"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "points": 30
    }
  ]
}
